Guide to the Duke Student Government Records, 1960-2019 UA.31.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA 2019-0098, circa 2006
  - Stephen Miller Discussing the Duke Rape Scandal, circa 2006; TRT 00:07:30. (Digital-materials UA31-02-0002-SET-0002, Video-file UA31020002-DVD-0001.mp4, Image-file UA31020002-DVD-0001.iso)
    DVD of Stephen Miller's appearances on Fox News and Headline Prime with Nancy Grace, discussing the Duke Men's Lacrosse Case of 2006.
- Board of Trustees Series [CLOSED], 1981, 1991-2004, 1 box
  Series comprises Board of Trustees files that were transferred from various accessions--see Restrictions note below. Arranged in chronological order regardless of accession date, except that certain like items are grouped together (such as a committee's meetings spanning several years). Original accession numbers appear on the individual folders.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [CLOSED UNTIL 2031-2054: Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.]
  - Report of Student Affairs Trustee Committee, 1981, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees. Student Affairs Trustee Committee Meetings, Agendas, and Supporting Documents, 1991-1996
    - 1991 Feb. 15 (Box 18)
    - 1991 Nov. 25 (Box 18)
    - 1992 Sept. 25 (Box 18)
    - 1992 Dec. 11 (Box 18)
    - 1993 Feb. 26 (Box 18)
    - 1994 May 6 (Box 18)
    - 1995 Sept. 29 (Box 18)
    - 1996 May 10 (Box 18)
    - 1996 Sept. 27 (Box 18)
    - 1997 May 16 (Box 18)
  - Trustee luncheons, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees--student orientation and meeting dates, 1994 (Box 18)
  - Trustee luncheons, 1994-1995 (Box 18)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1994 (Box 18)
    Contains reports to the BOT Committee on Institutional Advancement.
  - Keohane, Nan, Memo to Board of Trustees on residential and co-curricular life, 1994 Dec. 1 (Box 18)
  - Presentation to the Board of Trustees: "Plan for the Enhancement of Residential and Co-Curricular Life," 1994 Dec. 10 (Box 18)
  - DSG Report on Student Perspectives and "Plan for the Enhancement of Residential and Co-Curricular Life," approved by the BOT, 1994 Dec. 10 (Box 18)
  - Quadrangle Development Council and the "Plan for the Enhancement of Residential and Co-Curricular Life," approved by the BOT, 1994 Dec. 10 (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1995 Sept. 29-30 (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees. Business and Finance Committee minutes, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees, 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - Bianca Motley: VP Student Affairs (Board of Trustees files), 1996-1998, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 18)
  - Takcus Nesbit, Board of Trustees speech, 1997 May 16 (Box 18)
  - Duke Upperclass Residential Programming, Board of Trustees, 1998 Dec. 4, 1999 Feb. 26 (Box 18)
  - Student Standing Committees, Board of Trustees, 1999-2002 (Box 18)
  - BOT Business and Finance Committee Meeting, 2000 Oct. 6 (Box 18)
  - BOT Business and Finance Committee Meeting, 2000 Dec. 1 (Box 18)
  - Official Letters, 2000-2001 (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees, 2001-2002, 5 folders
    - BOT Meeting, Mr. Jordan Bazinsky, President, DSG, 2001 May 11-12 (Box 18)
    - BOT Meeting, Mr. C. J. Walsh, President, DSG, 2001 Oct. 5-6 (Box 18)
    - BOT Meeting, Mr. C. J. Walsh, President, DSG, 2002 Feb. 22-23 (Box 18)
    - BOT Meeting, Mr. Jean-Baptiste, President, DSG, 2002 Oct. 4-5 (Box 18)
    - BOT Meeting, Mr. Jean-Baptiste, President, DSG, 2002 Dec. 6-7 (Box 18)
  - Board of Trustees: Academic Affairs Committee, 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 18)
  - Student members of the Board of Trustees Standing Committees, 2003-2004 (Box 18)
  - BOT, Medical Center Affairs Committee--agendas, 2003 (Box 18)